Finding Aid for the Olive Percival Papers LSC.0119
UCLA Library Special Collections
- [22.] Music Books
  - 43. Mason, William. Spring-Dawn. New York: Beer & Schirmer, 1861 (?).; 198pp. 34.5 × 27 cm.; Cover stamped C.R. Hamblin.
  - 44. Bound volume, containing sheet music., 35.5 × 28 cm. No marks.